

LUKAS JURGILAS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

GET IN TOUCH

☐ Mobile: +4550307947 ☑ jurgilasslukas@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/lukas-jurgilas

PERSONAL SKILLS

- -Time management
- -Fast learner
- -Practical
- -Team worker
- -Motivated
- -Willing to move

LANGUAGES

- -Lithuanian (Native)
- -English (Speak, write, read, understand)
- -Danish (Limited skills)
- -Russian (Limited skills)

SKILLS

- -Java, C# (Intermediate)
- -. NET 5 (Intermediate)
- -HTML, CSS, React (Intermediate)
- -SQL (Novice)
- -Unity (Intermediate)
- -SCRUM
- -UMI

HOBBIES



ABOUT ME

I am 23 years – old, motivated, passionate, creative, communicative recent graduated software engineer. Always taking my tasks seriously with a motivation to do it as fast and as good as I can. Comfortable at analyzing problems and providing simple and effective solutions. A friendly, possessing urge to succeed and develop new skills in my field of interest.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- MITA-TEKNIK A/S, RØDKÆRSBRO Junior Software Engineer (part time) (2020.03 - 2021.12)
- EON REALITY DENMARK, VIBORG Software Engineering intern (2019.08 - 2020.01)
- VIA UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, DENMARK Student employee in Makerspace Viborg (2019.11 2020.01)
- RANDERS CITY CAMP, RANDERS, DENMARK Cleaning assistant (2019.07 2019.08)
- ÅRSTIDERNE A/S, BARRIT, DENMARK Bag machine operator in a warehouse (2018.02 2019.01)

EDUCATION

-VIA UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, DENMARK

Aug 2017 - Jan 2021 Recent graduate Bachelors degree in Software Engineering

-KLAIPĖDOS "ĄŽUOLYNO" GYMNASIUM, LITHUANIA

2014-2017 High school diploma